<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chao ZHOU on Chao ZHOU</title>
    <link>https://matzc.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chao ZHOU on Chao ZHOU</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2019 Chao ZHOU. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/talk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Fellows</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/researcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/researcher/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Students List</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/students/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/students/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/publication/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Animation for SelectNet method&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0021999121003399&#34;&gt;Gu, Yang and Zhou JCP 2021&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/50096157/93667843-7e1ed680-fabb-11ea-8da4-b13f7d7e5473.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Animation for SelectNet method:&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Left:&lt;/strong&gt; Green: SelectNet; Red: residual; Blue: solution error&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Right:&lt;/strong&gt; Red: residual v.s. iterations; Blue: solution error v.s. iterations&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second order BSDEs with quadratic growth, with Possamaï, D., Stochastic Processes and their Applications, 2013, 123(10):3770-3799.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second order reflected backward stochastic differential equations, with Matoussi, A., Possamaï, D., The Annals of Applied Probability, 2015, 23(6):2420-2457.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robust utility maximization in non-dominated models with 2BSDEs, with Matoussi, A., Possamaï, D., Mathematical Finance, 2015, 25(2):258-287.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second order backward stochastic differential equations with jumps: formulation and uniqueness, with Kazi-Tani, N., Possamaï, D., The Annals of Applied Probability, 2015, 25(5)2867-2908.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second order BSDEs with jumps: existence and probabilistic representation for fully-nonlinear PIDEs, with Kazi-Tani, N., Possamaï, D., Electronic Journal of Probability, 2015, 20(65):1-31.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The obstacle problem for semilinear parabolic partial integro-differential equations, with Matoussi, A., Sabbagh, W., Stochastics and Dynamics, 2015, 15(01)-1550007.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quadratic BSDEs with jumps: a fixed point approach, with Kazi-Tani, N., Possamaï, D., Electronic Journal of Probability, 2015, 20(66):1-28.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quadratic BSDEs with jumps: related non-linear expectations, with Kazi-Tani, N., Possamaï, D., Stochastics and Dynamics, 2016, 16(4)-1650012.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sustainable Black-Scholes equations, with Armenti, Y., Crépey, S., In: Londoño J., Garrido J., Jeanblanc M. (eds) Actuarial Sciences and Quantitative Finance. ICASQF 2016. Springer Proceedings in Mathematics &amp;amp; Statistics, 2017, vol 214: 155-167.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A unified approach to a priori estimates for supersolutions of BSDEs in general filtrations, with Bouchard, B., Possamaï, D., Tan, X., Annales de l&amp;rsquo;Institut Henri Poincare (B), 2018, 54(1):154-172.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stochastic control for a class of nonlinear kernels and applications, with Possamaï, D., Tan, X., The Annals of Probability, 2018, 46(1):551-603.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Constrained portfolio-consumption strategies with uncertain parameters and borrowing costs, with Yang, Z., Liang, G., Mathematics and Financial Economics, 2019, 13(3):393-427.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second order BSDE under monotonicity condition and liquidation problem under uncertainty, with Popier, A., The Annals of Applied Probability, 2019, 29(3):1685-1739.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second order stochastic target problems with generalized market impact, with B. Bouchard, G. Loeper and H. M. Soner, SIAM Journal on Control and Optimization, 2019, 57(6):4125-4149.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deep learning algorithm to solve portfolio management with proportional transaction cost, with W. Zhang, In CIFEr 2019 - IEEE Conference on Computational Intelligence for Financial Engineering and Economics, 2019, available online doi: 10.1109/CIFEr.2019.8759056.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bank monitoring incentives under moral hazard and adverse selection, with Hernández Santibáñez, N., Possamaï, D., Journal of Optimization Theory and Applications, 2020, 184(3):988-1035.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A risk-sharing framework of bilateral contracts, with J. Lee, S. Sturm, SIAM Journal on Financial Mathematics, 2020, 11(2):385-410.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Horizon-unbiased investment with ambiguity, with Q. Lin and X. Sun, Journal of Economic Dynamics and Control, 2020, 114, 103896, published online &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jedc.2020.103896&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jedc.2020.103896&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On dynamic programming principle for stochastic control under expectation constraints, with Y. Chow and X. Yu, Journal of Optimization Theory and Applications, 2020, 185:803-818.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lifetime ruin problem under high-watermark fees and drift uncertainty, with J. Lee and X. Yu, Applied Mathematics and Optimization, 2021, 84:2743-2773.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Binary funding impacts in derivative valuation, with J. Lee, Mathematical Finance, 2021, 31(1):242-278.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erratum for &amp;ldquo;Second-order reflected backward stochastic differential equations&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Second-order BSDEs with general reflection and game options under uncertainty&amp;rdquo;, with Matoussi, A., Possamaï, D., 2021. arXiv:1706.08588. The Annals of Applied Probability, 2021, 31(3):1505-1522.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gambling for resurrection and the heat equation on a triangle, with S. Ankirchner, C. Blanchet-Scalliet, and N. Kazi-Tani, Applied Mathematics and Optimization, 2021, 83(3):3111-3136.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Alpha-Heston stochastic volatility model, with Y. Jiao, C. Ma, and S. Scotti, Mathematical Finance, 2021, 31:943–978.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SelectNet: Self-paced learning for high-dimensional partial differential equations, with Y. Gu and H. Yang, Journal of Computational Physics, 2021, 441:110444.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Portfolio liquidation under factor uncertainty, with U. Horst and X. Xia, 2021, arXiv:1909.00748. The Annals of Applied Probability, 2022, 32(1):80-123.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Portfolio diversification and model uncertainty: a robust dynamic mean-variance approach, with H. Pham and X. Wei, Mathematical Finance, 2022, 32(1):349-404.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Numerical methods for mean field games based on Gaussian Processes and Fourier Features, with C. Mou and X. Yang, Journal of Computational Physics, 1 July 2022, 460:111188.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Power forward performance in semimartingale markets with stochastic integrated factors, with L. Bo and A. Capponi, 2022, &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1287/moor.2022.1262&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1287/moor.2022.1262&lt;/a&gt;. Mathematics of Operations Research, published online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Discovery of Dynamics via Linear Multistep Methods and Deep Learning: Error Estimation, with Q. Du, Y. Gu and H. Yang, 2022, arXiv:2103.11488. SIAM Journal on Numerical Analysis, 60(4):2014-2045.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mean Field Portfolio Games, with G. Fu, 2022, arXiv:2106.06185. Finance &amp;amp; Stochastics, 27, 189-231.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Backward Stochastic Differential Equations and Backward Stochastic Volterra Integral Equations with Anticipating Generators, with H. Wang and J. Yong, 2022, Probability, Uncertainty and Quantitative Risk, accepted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A learning scheme by sparse grids and Picard approximations for semilinear parabolic PDEs, with J.-F. Chassagneux, J. Chen and N. Frikha, 2022, arXiv:2102.12051. IMA Journal of Numerical Analysis, accepted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Linear-Quadratic Mean Field Games of Controls with Non-Monotone Data, with M. Li, C. Mou and Z. Wu, 2022, arXiv:2206.01732. Transactions of the American Mathematical Society (TAMS), accepted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robust control problems of BSDEs coupled with value functions, with Z. Yang and J. Zhang, 2022, arXiv:2208.10735, SIAM Journal on Financial Mathematics, accepted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Courses</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monte-Carlo method in finance and insurance&lt;/strong&gt; for 1st year graduate students at 2nd year undergraduate students at University of Maine, Le Mans, France, 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Probability and Statistics&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Multivariable Functions&lt;/strong&gt; for 2nd year undergraduate students at University of Maine, Le Mans, France, 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced Financial Mathematics&lt;/strong&gt; for M.Sc. in Mathematics at National University of Singapore, Singapore, 2013-2014&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Financial Time Series: Theory and Computation&lt;/strong&gt; for M.Sc.in Quantitative Finance at National University of Singapore, Singapore, 2013-2014, 2014-2015, 2015-2016&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interest Rate Models&lt;/strong&gt; for M.Sc. in Quantitative Finance at National University of Singapore, Singapore, 2013-2014, 2014-2015&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interest Rate Theory and Credit Risk&lt;/strong&gt; for M.Sc. in Quantitative Finance at National University of Singapore, Singapore, 2015-2016, 2016-2017, 2018-2019&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stochastic Analysis in Mathematical Finance&lt;/strong&gt; for M.Sc. in Mathematics and in Quantitative Finance at National University of Singapore, Singapore, 2014-2015, 2015-2016, 2016-2017, 2018-2019&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mathematical Finance&lt;/strong&gt; for Undergraduates and M.Sc. in Mathematics and in Quantitative Finance at National University of Singapore, Singapore, 2016-2017, 2017-2018, 2018-2019&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TA in both &lt;strong&gt;Optimization&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Numerical Analysis&lt;/strong&gt; for 1st year students at ENSAE (Paris Graduate School of Economics, Statistics and Finance), France, 2009-2010&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seminars &amp; Conferences</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/conference/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The 6th Asian Quantitative Finance Conference&lt;/strong&gt;, China, Guangzhou, November 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workshop on Stochastic Analysis, Stochastic Control and New Developments&lt;/strong&gt;, China, Weihai, August 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workshop Mathematics of Behavioral Economics and Knightian Uncertainty in Financial Markets&lt;/strong&gt;, Germany, Bielefeld, May 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workshop on Stochastic Analysis&lt;/strong&gt;, Italy, Verona, May 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workshop on Stochastic Control and Related Issues Kansai University&lt;/strong&gt;, Japan, Osaka, March 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workshop on Stochastic Analysis applied to economics, finance and insurance&lt;/strong&gt;, Chile, Santiago, March 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workshop on BSDEs, SPDEs and their applications&lt;/strong&gt;, United Kingdom, Edinburgh, July 2017&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conference Asymptotic Statistics of Stochastic Processes and Applications&lt;/strong&gt;, Russia, Peterhof, July 2017&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workshop on Stochastic Analysis in Finance&lt;/strong&gt;, China, Hong Kong, May 2017&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3rd Berlin-Princeton-Singapore Workshop on Quantitative Finance&lt;/strong&gt;, Germany, Berlin, April 2017&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The 5th Asian Quantitative Finance Conference&lt;/strong&gt;, South Korea, Seoul, April 2017&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Berlin-Princeton-Singapore Workshop on Quantitative Finance&lt;/strong&gt;, United State, Princeton, July 2016&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Journe´es de Probabilities&lt;/strong&gt; 2016, France, Le Mans, May 2016&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frontiers in Stochastic Modelling for Finance&lt;/strong&gt;, Italy, Padua, February 2016&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Fourth Asian Quantitative Finance Conference&lt;/strong&gt;, Japan, Osaka, February 2016&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;International Workshop on Analysis and Control of Stochastic Partial Differential Equations&lt;/strong&gt;, China, Shanghai, November 2015&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Singapore-Suzhou Workshop on Quantitative Finance&lt;/strong&gt;, China, Suzhou, July 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE 7TH INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON BACKWARD STOCHASTIC DIFFERENTIAL EQUATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;, Weihai, 22-27 June 2014 &lt;a href=&#34;http://211.86.56.196/BSDE2014/&#34;&gt;site&lt;/a&gt;, invited speaker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Labex Louis Bachelier - SIAM-SMAI Conference on Financial Mathematics: Advanced Modeling and Numerical Methods&lt;/strong&gt;, Paris, 17-20 June 2014 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ceremade.dauphine.fr/ModelsRisks/conference.html&#34;&gt;site&lt;/a&gt;, invited speaker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The First Berlin-Singapore Workshop on Quantitative Finance and Financial Risk&lt;/strong&gt;, Berlin, 21-24 May 2014 &lt;a href=&#34;http://cqf.nus.edu.sg/First_Berlin-Singapore_Workshop-QFFR2014/Overview.html&#34;&gt;site&lt;/a&gt;, invited speaker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMS Summer Program: Nonlinear Expectations, Stochastic Calculus under Knightian Uncertainty, and Related Topics&lt;/strong&gt;, Singapore, Singapore, June-July 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summer program: Nonlinear Expectations, Stochastic Calculus under Knightian Uncertainty, and Related Topics&lt;/strong&gt;, Singapore, 3 June-12 July, 2013 site, invited speaker.
The First Asian Quantitative Finance Conference, Singapore, NUS, 9-11 January 2013 &lt;a href=&#34;http://www2.ims.nus.edu.sg/Programs/013wnlinear/index.php&#34;&gt;site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fifth SMAI European Summer School In Financial Mathematics&lt;/strong&gt;, Paris, Ecole Polytechnique 27-31 August 2012 &lt;a href=&#34;http://cqf.nus.edu.sg/AQFC2013/aqfc2013.htm&#34;&gt;site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bachelier Finance Society 7th World Congress&lt;/strong&gt;, Sydney 12-22 June 2012 &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bfs2012.com/&#34;&gt;site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Sixth Bachelier Colloquium&lt;/strong&gt;, Metabief-France 15-22 January 2012 &lt;a href=&#34;http://ykabanov.perso.math.cnrs.fr/Bachelier2012/programmes%20angl/programme2_B3_ang.html&#34;&gt;site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marie Curie Initial Training Network Spring School &amp;ldquo;Stochastic Analysis in Finance&lt;/strong&gt;, Roscoff-France 06-15 March 2012 &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.math.univ-brest.fr/perso/rainer.buckdahn/March%202012/Spring%20School%20mars%202012.html&#34;&gt;site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminaire de Probabilite Institut de Recherche Mathematique de Rennes&lt;/strong&gt;, Rennes-France 06 February 2012 &lt;a href=&#34;http://irmar.univ-rennes1.fr/Equipes/aleatoire/Procstoc/seminaire/&#34;&gt;site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sino-French Summer Institute: Stochastic Modeling and Applications&lt;/strong&gt;, Beijing-China, 13 Juin-1st July 2011 &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.amt.ac.cn/sino-french2010/index.htm&#34;&gt;site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/project/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/author/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/author/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/slides/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
