<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Research Fellows on Chao ZHOU</title>
    <link>https://matzc.github.io/researcher/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Research Fellows on Chao ZHOU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2019 Chao ZHOU. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matzc.github.io/researcher/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hanxiao WANG</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/researcher/hanxiao/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/researcher/hanxiao/</guid>
      <description>My Info Currently, I am a Research Fellow at National University of Singapore, working with the Department of Mathematics. My research focuses on stochastic control, stochastic analysis and mathematical finance.
I received my Ph.D. in 2020 at Fudan University (in China) on my thesis about backward stochastic Volterra integral equations and stochastic linear-quadratic optimal control problems. Before I started my Ph.D. program, I had received a Bachelor degree in Jilin University (in China).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huafu LIAO</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/researcher/huafu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/researcher/huafu/</guid>
      <description>My Info I am currently a Research Fellow in National University of Singapore. My research interests are in credit risk, optimal porfolio selection with regime switching, and neural network.
I received my Ph.D Degree in Mathematics from University of Science and Technology of China in 2019. My Ph.D thesis studies a class of dynamical models on credit portfolio with regime-switching and default contagion, utilizing recursive HJB system and BSDE with jumps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yiqi GU</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/researcher/yiqi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/researcher/yiqi/</guid>
      <description>Bio Currently, I am a Research Fellow at National University of Singapore, working with the Department of Mathematics. My research focuses on deep learning-based methods for partial differential equations.
I received my Ph.D. in 2019 at Purdue University (in US) on my thesis about spectral methods for PDEs in complex domains. Before I started my Ph.D. program, I had received a Bachelor degree in Zhejiang University (in China) and a Master degree in University of Washington (in US).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guanxing FU</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/researcher/guanxing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/researcher/guanxing/</guid>
      <description>Bio I am an Assistant Professor in The Hong Kong Polytechnic University, see my website
Previously, I was a Research Fellow in National University of Singapore. Here I was working on mean field games, stochastic control and mathematical finance.
I obtained my PhD degree from Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin in 2018. My PhD thesis focuses on mean field games arising in optimal portfolio liquidation, mean field games with singular controls as well as BSPDEs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
