<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Students List on Chao ZHOU</title>
    <link>https://matzc.github.io/students/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Students List on Chao ZHOU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2019 Chao ZHOU. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matzc.github.io/students/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hanxiao WANG</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/students/hanxiao/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/students/hanxiao/</guid>
      <description>My Info Currently, I am a Research Fellow at National University of Singapore, working with the Department of Mathematics. My research focuses on stochastic control, stochastic analysis and mathematical finance.
I received my Ph.D. in 2020 at Fudan University (in China) on my thesis about backward stochastic Volterra integral equations and stochastic linear-quadratic optimal control problems. Before I started my Ph.D. program, I had received a Bachelor degree in Jilin University (in China).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huafu LIAO</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/students/huafu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/students/huafu/</guid>
      <description>My Info I am currently a Research Fellow in National University of Singapore. My research interests are in credit risk, optimal porfolio selection with regime switching, and neural network.
I received my Ph.D Degree in Mathematics from University of Science and Technology of China in 2019. My Ph.D thesis studies a class of dynamical models on credit portfolio with regime-switching and default contagion, utilizing recursive HJB system and BSDE with jumps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jiayu SHI</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/students/jiayu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/students/jiayu/</guid>
      <description>My Info I am a Ph.D. student at the National University of Singapore, under the supervision of Prof. ZHOU Chao and Prof. TOH Kim-Chuan.
  CV
  Email: shi.jiayu@u.nus.edu
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tang Siu Hin</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/students/tang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/students/tang/</guid>
      <description>My Info I am a PhD student at NUS under the supervision of Dr. Chao ZHOU.
  Email: s.h.tang@u.nus.edu
  CV
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mengge LI</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/students/mengge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/students/mengge/</guid>
      <description>I am a PhD candidate at the National University of Singapore, under the supervision of Dr. Chao ZHOU.
My Info   Email: li.mengge@u.nus.edu
  CV
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junbeom Lee</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/students/junbeom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/students/junbeom/</guid>
      <description>Bio Currently, I am a Quant Trader at Yuanta Securities(Seoul, South Korea)
I was a research fellow working with the Department of Mathematics in the National University of Singapore.
I received my Ph.D. in 2018 on my thesis about XVA. Before I started my Ph.D. program, I had worked for a finance company as a quant for 2 years.
My Info  Email: junbeoml22@gmail.com Github LinkedIn CV  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meixia LIN</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/students/meixia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/students/meixia/</guid>
      <description>Ph.D student in Department of Mathematics, under the supervision of Kim-Chuan TOH and Chao ZHOU.
My Info   Email: lin_meixia@u.nus.edu
  CV
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tan Hong Ming</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/students/hongming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/students/hongming/</guid>
      <description>Bio I am a PhD candidate at the Institute of Operations Research and Analytics, IORA, NUS.
My research interest is decision making under uncertainty, bayesian learning, pricing revenue management, and sport analytics.
I am interested to learn about the optimal actions people or companies should take when faced with uncertainty about the consequences of events. I mainly use analytical models to approach my research questions.
My Info   Email: thm@u.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weiwei ZHANG</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/students/weiwei/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/students/weiwei/</guid>
      <description>My Info   Email: e0046913@u.nus.edu
  CV
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xizhi Su</title>
      <link>https://matzc.github.io/students/xizhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matzc.github.io/students/xizhi/</guid>
      <description>Bio I am a PhD student at the National University of Singapore. My advisors are Dr. Chao Zhou and Prof Min Dai.
My current research projects are portfolio optimization under information frictions and singular controls applied in finance. I am also interested in applications of deep neural networks.
Before coming to Singapore, I have completed a Master’s degree from Part III at Cambridge University. My essay advisor was Professor Frank P.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
